evosite.co.uk 2017-09-12

# Privacy Policy | Evosite eCommerce Agency

### What is this privacy policy for?

This privacy policy is for this website www.evosite.co.uk and served by Evosite Ltd and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.

The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owners.

Furthermore the way this website processes, store and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.

### The Website

This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience.  This website complies to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.

### Use of Cookies

This website uses cookies to better the users experience whilst visiting the website.  Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer/device.  This complies with recent legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user's computer/device.

Cookies are small files saved to the user's computer's hard drive that track, save and store information about the user's interactions and usage of the website.  This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.

Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use of saving of cookies from this website onto their computer's hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and it's external serving vendors.

This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it.  This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computer's hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information.  You can read Google's privacy policy for further information: <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

Other cookies may be stored to your computer's hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts .  Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer.  No personal information is stored, saved or collected.

### Contact & Communication

Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk.  Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.

This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products/services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. This includes using your details to subscribe you to any email newsletter program the website operates but only if this was made clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process.  Or whereby you the consumer have previously purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the company a product or service that the email newsletter relates to.  This is by no means an entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing material.  Your details are not passed on to any third parties.

### External Links

Although this website oly looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users are advised to adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website.  (External links are clickable text/banner/image links to other websites, similar to; Folded Book Art or Used Model Trains For Sale.)  The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts.  Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and it's owners cannot be held liable for any damage or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.
